Not yet. So we wait on Ben and you think or should be calling it? I'll just like you
No, I did
I want to call it order today's where you're me or mine, especially if you tell your daughter for today's day
Have the invocation there's by the pastor of apostolic church filled shires. How are you gonna?
Thank you. Appreciate the opportunity to come and open up city council meeting with prayer. It's a wonderful thing in the day we live in to just acknowledge God in that which we do and I commend
The council and
For allowing this to happen. I really I don't know if you get that a lot but I appreciate it
If you would buy your heads with me father, we thank you for living in a town
Which acknowledges you in their their council meetings. We ask you give the leaders here wisdom and to lead and to guide and direct and legislate
To the benefit of our community lord. We thank you for those who serve in the civil parts of the community whether it be the fire the police the MTs
We thank you for their service lord and for all those that are behind the scene in the administration ward. There's a lot that takes there's a lot that makes the city work together for good
And we appreciate the city leaders and we just ask you to bless them. Bless this meeting. Bless our city. Let your grace fall upon us in Jesus name. Amen.
For those public input unscheduled personal pictures and one of the audience the list is to address the authority on any of the agenda
I
Number five is claims in the amount of 1,811,018317 as described on the attached claims list
If there are no questions we'd entertain a motion to approve. First we'll print my answer second. Second. Go call please
Johnson. Forster.
All right.
Wesson.
I'm seven or excuse me.
I'm six is a war that bid number of C 17 dash by five in the amount of 95,996 to John Vance auto group.
Approach us assembly and delivery of a new water truck on the 4 by 4 crew cab chassis Mr. Stevens.
How are you tonight?
We're purchasing a strap to replace a 1998 model international. We have we've had quite a few things we've had to fix on it.
Speed on her all that does not work on this truck. Got quite a bit of rest.
use and right now I've got two queries and they fight over who gets the newest truck right now.
So I was wanting to get this out of the truck to replace the 98 model.
Okay, Dean, was just a purchase or release?
This is a lease.
Well actually we're purchasing, but we're purchasing over a period of time.
It's not an immediate purchase.
And was this somewhere in our budget?
Yes, it is.
Okay.
Good.
Any questions for Dean or Chris?
In case somebody's watching, does it know what is a water truck?
It's just a service truck that we carry all our tools on and has a hydraulic pump that
we can run our hydraulic pumps to pump water out of the hole that also has a place for
our electric pumps where we can use them.
So it's for the water to pump.
Yes.
And it's got an air compressor to run our tools as far as impacts and stuff to put clamps and stuff
on.
It's got a place to store the clamps.
It's just, the other one's just worn out.
It's time for a new one.
So it's not just a big pickup truck, it's got a lot of, it's got a great central tools that you need.
And it's got a great big old bed on it with a bunch of bands on it, so it is.
Dean, do you have something to do with this?
I'm not going to ask you if the one you're getting a read of, what can we be doing with that?
We probably will be selling you that in an auction.
Okay.
Is this new one going to have some updated features which you haven't even had?
Yeah.
The other one didn't have hydraulics.
We had hydraulic pack on the back and it's worn out.
It takes some sort of an entry needed that you always just have to have.
They didn't have the automatic grill where you could pull it out.
You had to unwind hose and you had to wind it back up.
This has a lot of good features that the other truck does not have.
It's all right.
Another question?
Okay.
So we have a motion to approve a worrying bit of number C-17-55.
I'll make the motion.
And in a second?
Second.
We'll publish.
Listen.
Four.
Five.
Lewis.
Johnson.
Okay.
All right.
Thanks, Chris.
I'm seven a world US Bank Leasing Services for a agreement of number C-17-55 for the
water truck that we just talked about in the 903-470 over five year payment.
That's to make payments of 1744-502.
So Dean, I guess the difference in the purchase price and the agreement with US Bank
Leasing is the...
I guess that's correct.
Okay.
So we need a motion to approve the leasing services.
That's good.
And I'll submit that work, please.
Johnson.
Schultz.
Lewis.
Hi.
Question.
Four.
All right.
Any new business Dean?
No, no.
Who else?
Staff, a quarter in your packet.
Any questions for staff?
Any community announcements from trustees?
We have most to adjourn.
I'm sure you're adjourned.
And a second.
That's all.
Please.
Western.